

SELAHATTIN SERDAR HELLI

CONTACT

Mobile: +905347760725

• Ataşehir/İstanbul

https://serdarhelli.github.io/

PROGRAMMING SKILS

- Python (Advanced); Numpy, Keras, Tensorflow, Pandas, Stats. Model, Scikit-Learn, OpenCV, PIL libraries
- SQL(Intermediate)
- HTML5 and CSS (Intermediate)
- C++(Intermediate)

PERSONAL

Machine learning/Deep learning, image processing, data science, computer vision, software development, and numerical analysis are the subjects that I have been studying for 2 years. In line with these subjects, my purposes are: to improve my abilities, skills, to learn new technologies, and to reach a successful career.

SKILLS

- Foreing Language English
- The ability to analyze complex technical information
- The competency of analyze, design and implementing artifical intellegence structures
- Detail oriented
- Strong communication

REFERENCES

Yeditepe University Asist.Prof.Dr Andaç HAMAMCI E – andac.hamamci@yeditepe.edu.tr P – 0 (216) 578 00 49

Software Developer at Huawei Muhammed Enes Durmuş E – mnsdurmus@gmail.com P – 0 532 501 68 17

EDUCATION HISTORY

YEDITEPE UNIVERSITY

- · Master's Degree, Data Science 2020-2022
- · Bachelor of Science, Biomedical Engineering 2015-2020

MACHINE LEARNING PROJECTS

- Automatic Semantic Segmentation In One-Shot Panoramic Dental X-Ray Images Using Deep Learning with U-Net(Fully Connective Convolutional Neural Networks)
- Medical Image Classification with VGG-19
- Natural Language Process Text Classification On Posted Tweets Are About The Violence To Woman Or Not.
- Short-Term Forecasting COVID-19 Cases In Turkey Using Long Short-Term Memory Network
- · Automatation Drawing Merchant Lines And Angles With Artificial Intelligence

MEMBERSHIPS AND VOLUNTEER WORKS

- Member of IEEE(The Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers)
- Member of EMBS (IEEE Engineering in Medicine and Biology)
- BIOMATE(Biomedical Engineering Conference with IEEE)

CERTIFICATIONS

 $\bullet \ \ \text{``Neural Networks and Deep Learning''} \ \ \text{an online non-credit course authorized by deeplearning.ai}$

WORK EXPERIENCE

INTERNSHIPS

Yeditepe Üniversitesi Diş Hastanesi | 2018 - 2019

- Modified existing device to correct errors and optimize efficiency
- Prepared detailed reports
- Provided technical support for device hardware and software

As an intern in a dental clinic, I had the opportunity to learn about many dental devices, computer vision software, and clinical databases. During my internship, I was interested in the installation, repairing, maintenance of medical devices.

Intern in a IT Consultancy –Mega Bilgi İletişim | 2013 – 2014 During my internship, I provided technical support for computer hardware and software to the companies and their employee. The componies were such as "Turkon Holding", "ITS. Caleb Brett Deniz Survey A.Ş.".

PUBLICATIONS

 S.Serdar HELLİ,Çağkan DEMİRCİ,Onur ÇOBAN, Andaç HAMAMCI."Short-Term Forecasting COVID-19 Cases In Turkey Using Long Short-Term Memory Network", 2020 Medical Technologies Congress (TIPTEKNO). IEEE, 2020 (accepted)